ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
Ack!
What? Did that really happen?
Are you serious?
Yes, and that's why I said…
Oh, good morning, Mrs. Forger.
Why are you looking so glum?
Am I going to be cast aside?
What?
Come to think about it,
who cares if I won against her in tennis?
What's wrong with her?
I bet her husband cheated on her.
-I have no doubt about it!
-What a horrible man!
What?
He's handsome, so it can't be helped.
I bet women are chasing after him
like flies.
Let's hope Mrs. Forger doesn't report him
to the secret police
like that lady in apartment 15.
Huh?!
Yor… are you worried about Nightfall?
This is not good. It's giving off
a bad impression to the neighbors too.
And if by any chance she talks
to her brother about it…
That's what happened.
That damn bastard!
Let's execute him at once! We'll get
the State Security Service involved!
I could see that happening!
MISSION 24: MOTHER AND WIFE
I've got you cornered, Bondman!
Bad King Scruffy!
Anya's going to draw now.
I'll give you a special color changing pen
that I invented.
Oh, and I also brought a frisbee
for the dog.
I want to play too!
All right, I'll leave her in your care.
Have fun--
How many times do I have to tell you
that I'm not your babysitter!
I already told you.
I have to clear up Yor's misunderstanding,
or it will affect this mission.
Have your family meeting at home!
It's hard to have that kind of
conversation in front of a kid!
And here you go.
Don't think you can solve everything
with money!
All right everyone, let's go to the park!
-Let's enjoy ourselves!
-Yeah!
Yor.
I'm sorry, I got off late
because I had to work overtime.
I'm glad you're off now.
Did you have some plans today…
How about we go out for some drinks?
I know a good place.
Here's your Red Queen.
-Thank you.
-I'll have my usual.
Bottle of scotch, please.
Thanks for always looking after
the house and Anya.
-Cheers.
-Oh?
Ch… cheers.
What's going on?
It feels like he has
something to say to me.
Thanks for your hard work until now.
I'll be moving on with my new wife!
-Good evening.
-Oops.
Could that be it?
By the way,
I wanted to talk to you about Fiona.
Wha--
-Yor?
-I'm sorry.
What should I do? This is a problem.
If he ends this relationship…
He's right.
This so-called marriage is
for our mutual benefit.
I don't have the right to stick my head
into Loid's private business.
Um…
If Loid has become rather close
with that person,
then I should gracefully withdraw myself.
Um… Loid…
If it's your wish…
then I'd be happy to…
Um…
What? Why can't I say it?
-Um…
-Hm?
My words keep getting caught in my throat.
Is it because I want this life
to continue?
No, Yor! It's not about you.
Think about Loid's happiness.
I must tell him that!
Alcohol! Give me strength!
Open up my throat!
It's not enough!
Give me some of yours, Loid!
Yor, you'll die if you drink like that!
Loid…
Who is that woman?
Do you like her?
I was about to explain that right now.
Oh I see, so you two
are in a relationship after all, huh?
-I was planning to wish you happiness.
-Calm down, Yor.
But what in the world am I doing?
She's just my co-worker.
We're nothing more than that.
Being popular has its difficulties.
I know I'm a useless woman.
I'm not pretty like Fiona either.
Did you hear what I said?
Hold on…
But you said before that I was pretty.
Was that a lie?
I thought Yor was belittling
her own abilities
and assumed that I wanted to
end this relationship, but…
Is this jealousy?
Did you get tired of me?
Does Yor have romantic feelings
towards me?
I'm Twilight.
I've had relationships with
countless women for my missions.
I'm sorry for making you worry…
Yor.
If Yor has feelings for me,
then I should take advantage
of those feelings.
In other words, a honey trap!
I want you to trust me.
Do you hate me?
No… not at all…
Yor, being by your side all this time
has made me realize my true feelings.
Um… Loid…
Loid…
I want this marriage to be real--
Oh, what have I done?
I was wrong!
That blow right now…
That power wasn't from embarrassment.
It was rejection!
She has no romantic feelings for me!
I was so full of myself! I'm so sorry!
Loid, are you all right?
I don't understand. Why was
she acting that way just now?
Was it some advanced reverse trap
to instigate a honey trap?
Is Yor a spy too? No, calm down Twilight.
That's impossible.
-But what have I done…
-I'm so sorry!
Yor has a way of throwing me off…
Go to sleep beneath…
-A song?
-The silver light…
How nostalgic.
It's a lullaby I used to hear.
My cute little Prince, go to sleep
Mom…
I don't know the rest of the lyrics
Whoa!
Good morning, Loid.
Where am I?
How long have I been out?
We're at a nearby park.
The bartender said that we were too loud,
and kicked us out.
You were sleeping for about five minutes.
I haven't been knocked unconscious
ever since I trained with my mentor!
You're losing your edge, Twilight!
Why was I sleeping on her lap?
I'm so sorry, Loid.
I don't blame you for wanting to
abandon someone like me,
who only has physical strength.
When I was little…
I don't remember my mom's face anymore,
but I remember how I loved
being in her arms.
Even on nights when bombs could
fall on us at any given time,
I was able to sleep peacefully
as long as my mom was by my side.
My mom was strong.
Anya always says,
"Even when I'm in danger,
I'll be okay because Mother will save me."
She can have fun with a smile on her face,
because you give her a sense of security.
You're able to create a world
that the government organizations
have been spilling blood, sweat
and tears to create.
Yor, you're strong.
It might be rude to say this
to a single lady,
but you're already a wonderful mother.
I may be strong,
but it's of a different sort…
I have absolutely no intention
of finding your replacement.
But Fiona is much more…
Even if she were to play the role
of a mother,
she has zero parenting skills.
I only know what I know
because I always took care of Yuri.
That's all I'm doing…
That's right!
That's an unmatched skill
that you've honed
through years of experience.
You should be proud of that!
I'd be happy if you can continue playing
the role of Anya's mother.
And also, the role of my wife.
I will happily accept.
If you're okay with someone like me.
Yor, your nose is running.
I'm sorry for being such a mess.
Let's go home.
Yes, let's! When we get home,
I'll make some warm tea.
Mother and Father are late.
I think they're hooking up somewhere.
Where did you learn that word?
Mostly Becky.
When are they coming back?
Do you love your dad and mom?
Yeah, I love them.
I see.
We're back.
Father and Mother,
were you two being lovey… dovey…
What happened? Did you get punched
when you made your move?
That's not it! It's my fault…
A chin monster.
Take a good look at it!
Don't touch it!
I told you not to touch it!
I'm surprised at myself too…
Back then,
I was not attached to anything
except my younger brother.
But now, I find myself not wanting to
let go of what I have right now.
The next day.
Loid, what happened to your chin?!
What? No way!
You forgot everything about last night?
They had the same discussion
one more time.
Next week is finally the reception.
Oh…
It has nothing to do with us for now.
I'll collect eight Stella Stars
in no time.
I'm sure!
Father needs to become friends with
the second son's dad for Operation Sticks.
In order for that to happen,
Anya needs to become
an Imperial Scholar
and attend the reception.
But Anya has given up a bit on collecting
eight Stella Stars.
Studying,
and sports are not my strong suit,
so I'm starting to lose heart.
So I moved onto Plan B,
and placed my bet on
becoming friends with the second son,
but that's not going well lately.
What are you looking at, you brat?
Daughter of a violent and corrupt doctor!
This is frustrating.
I'm getting frustrated looking at you,
Anya!
I understand, Anya!
It's hard to tell someone that
you love them, right?
Love?
I love Father.
I love Mother.
I love peanuts.
I love anime.
Second son.
No. Not at all.
Stop being so shy.
Be honest with yourself!
I've got an idea!
I'll help you so that he'll start
liking you!
Huh?
Men are always deceived by
outward appearances.
Just dress up and look cute,
and he'll be all over you.
Oh…
So on our next day off…
Let's go shopping together!
It's Anya's first time in a luxury car!
How exciting!
It's pretty comfortable, right?
By the way,
I went to your house to pick you up,
but why wasn't Mr. Loid home?
Mr. Loid? Where is Mr. Loid?
Please have a nice day out
with my daughter.
Father had an emergency situation at work.
Mr. Loid's wife is prettier in person
than in the picture.
She's a formidable rival!
You must not get involved in an affair.
By the way, that's a cute handbag.
What's inside?
Um… lots of cash.
It'll be advantageous to build
a good relationship with the Blackbells.
I'm sure I can write this off
as an expense.
-Take this.
-That much?!
-It's my allowance.
-Oh my, Mr. Loid is so kind!
Even though it's not much.
Kids these days!
How many peanuts can I buy with this?
We're not going to buy any peanuts!
We're buying clothes! Got it?
Welcome, Madam Becky.
We prepared many items
from the newest Berlint Collection.
Thank you!
Becky, is your family
the ruler of the underground world?
How much cash do you have?
I've never carried cash before in my life.
Usually, the shops bring things
to my house.
But I want to enjoy shopping
with you today,
so I rented out this department store.
Let's try on lots of clothes,
and find an outfit to make him
fall in love with you.
ANYA AUTUMN/WINTER COLLECTION
OUTFIT TO MAKE YOUR CLASSMATE FALL IN LOVE
Wonderful! That's awesome, Anya!
You're so cute!
Although not as cute as me.
That's right, Anya! Break out of
that shell and reinvent yourself!
Maybe you broke through that shell
a little too much…
But one must be adventurous
to become fashionable!
That's great, Anya! You're starting
to grow into that look!
Go beyond the boundaries of fashion!
Being fashionable is hard work.
Yeah, we don't know his preferred taste,
so it's hard to make a choice.
Come to think of it, Anya wears
the same clothes every day to school.
I won't have a chance to show off
these outfits.
Of course, you wear the same clothes.
That's called a uniform.
There's a hall party
at the end of the semester.
If the teachers allow it,
we can choose our own outfits.
That's your chance!
Oh, I just remembered!
If the party allows the parents to attend…
Hello, beautiful madam.
I'm Loid, Anya's father.
What have I been doing?
I don't have time to be
picking out Anya's outfit!
No way!
Tell me, what kind of clothes
does Mr. Loid like?
-So cute!
-How lovely.
Does he prefer the classic "cute" type?
Madam, you're so lovely!
-How cute!
-Wow!
Or does he prefer
the "runway fashion" type?
So lovely!
How about this?
Or should I go all out for a mature look?
Oh, you look so mature!
Or should I dress up like his wife?
-That look suits you!
-How cute!
I don't know anymore.
All of them looked lovely on you.
I'll buy all of them.
Thank you.
Which will you choose, Anya?
Anya's had enough of clothes.
Really? Then should we go look
for some shoes?
Even I'm a little tired now.
Anya was about to shop herself to death.
Shop yourself to death? You're dying?
Madam, you've bought too much.
Martha? Are you behind all this stuff?
By the way Anya, you haven't
bought anything yet.
I don't know what I want.
Fashion is so hard.
Is shopping…
not fun for you?
It's fun!
This is Anya's first time shopping
with a friend! It's exciting!
A friend?
All right, now that's settled,
let's get back to work!
Let's find out what you want, Anya.
Anya is drawn to anime products.
There are no such things
in this department store.
There's a shop over there that sells
stuffed animals.
What is this sheep?
That's this department store's mascot.
See that? It's because they started their
business by selling wool.
It's so cute.
-Anya wants to buy that.
-What? A keychain?
Anya, you're such a kid.
It's to commemorate my shopping trip
with Becky!
It's proof that we survived
the shopping of death.
Then I'll get…
Listen up, Becky.
You're the daughter of the Blackbell
family so you must only wear the finest.
Here you go. I got one for you too, Becky.
What? When?
-Anya is like an older sister.
-But…
Rejecting a friend's kindness,
will bring disgrace to
the Blackbell household.
I'm sure your father will say
the same thing.
I guess I have no choice.
It's embarrassing,
but I'll accept it for you.
-Thanks.
-You should be honest with yourself too.
Why did we come shopping today anyway?
-I forget.
-Oh, who cares. Let's go now.
It's all Becky's fault!
She bullies everyone
by saying mean things!
What's wrong with calling them brats?
They're all acting like one!
Stop it, Madam.
Eden Academy? No way!
I learned at pre-school
that there's no merit to
hanging out with low-bred people.
What a nightmare. Oh well.
I guess grinning and bearing it
is all a part of becoming an adult.
Madam, you must not think
that you know everything and everyone.
Admitting that you don't know,
is the first step to becoming an adult.
Listen, Martha!
There's an interesting girl in my class!
That school isn't so bad after all.
I'll give you something in return…
I'm so happy for you, Madam.
This thing costs 300 dalc?!
It matches with Becky's.
I'm jelly…
Good morning!
-Anya!
-Good morning.
-Matching!
-Yes, we're matching!
I hope the teachers won't get mad.
-It shouldn't be a problem.
-You're right.
What's the matter, Damian?
It's nothing!
MISSION 25: FIRST CONTACT
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita